Kheel, Theodore W. Arbitration files 6021/003
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- TWU Local 100 and Queens Transit Corp. and Steinway Transit corp. (A. Rafferty et al.), 1974 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  Jan 3
- TWU Local 100 and Queens Transit and Steinway Transit Creation of New Position, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 23)
- TWU Local 100 and Queens Transit Corp. (Road Reliefs and Swing runs), 1983 (Box 19, Folder 24)
- TWU Local 225 and Gray Line New York Tours corp. Contract Provisions, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 25)
- TWU Local 252 and Green Bus Lines, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 26)
- TWU Local 252 and Metropolitan Suburban Bus Authority Memos and Correspondences, 1959-1983 (Box 19, Folder 27)
- TWU Local 252 and Metropolitan suburban Bus Authority, Original Awards, 1974-1980 (Box 19, Folder 28)
- TWU Local 252 and Metropolitan suburban Bus company Award Drafts, 1974-1981 (Box 19, Folder 29)
- TWU Local 252 and Metropolitan Suburban Bus Authority Herbert Smith, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 30)
- TWU Local 252 and Metropolitan Suburban Bus Authority, Memos and Correspondence (2), 1974-1978 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  June 28, 1974 - Aug 3, 1978
- TWU Local 252 Metropolitan Suburban Bus Authority, Copy of Opinions, 1975-1979 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- TWU Local 252 Metropolitan Suburban Bus Authority, Terance McManus, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- TWU Local 252 Metropolitan Suburban Bus Authority, Larry Horton, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- TWU Local 252 Metropolitan Suburban Bus Authority, Union Representation Sharing run at Zahr's location, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- TWU Local 252 Metropolitan Suburban Bus Authority, Joseph Catucci, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- TWU Local 252 Metropolitan Suburban Bus Authority, Herbert Jackson, et al., 1977 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- TWU Local 252 Metropolitan Suburban Bus Authority, Herbert Jackson, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  May 4
- TWU Local 252 Metropolitan Suburban Bus Authority, Harold Aycock, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  Aug 6
- TWU Local 252 Metropolitan Suburban Bus Authority, Foster Bryant, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  Aug 16
- TWU Local 252 Metropolitan Suburban Bus Authority, John Cannizzaro, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- TWU Local 252 Metropolitan Suburban Bus Authority, Lawrence Redick, Sr. et al., 1979 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- TWU Local 252 Metropolitan Suburban Bus Authority, Foster Bryant, et al., 1979 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- TWU Local 252 Metropolitan Suburban Bus Authority, Vacation Picks, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- TWU Local 252 Metropolitan Suburban Bus Authority, Philip Means, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- TWU Local 252 Metropolitan Suburban Bus Authority, Samuel Barr, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- TWU Local 252 Metropolitan Suburban Bus Authority, Ernest Parker, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- TWU Local 252 Metropolitan Suburban Bus Authority, Subcontracting`, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- TWU Local 252 Metropolitan Suburban Bus Authority, Lawrence trapaso, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- TWU Local 252 Metropolitan Suburban Bus Authority, Kevin Molloy, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- TWU Local 252 Metropolitan Suburban Bus Authority, Lawrence Redick, Sr. et al., 1980 (Box 20, Folder 21)
- TWU Local 252 Metropolitan Suburban Bus Authority, Frank Ponzio, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 22)
- TWU Local 252 Metropolitan Suburban Bus Authority, Maurice Johnson, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 23)
- TWU Local 252 Metropolitan Suburban Bus Authority, Talton Hughes, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  Sept 29
- TWU Local 252 Metropolitan Suburban Bus Authority, Augusta Ware, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 25)
- TWU Local 252 Metropolitan Suburban Bus Authority, George Arnold, Sr., 1980 (Box 20, Folder 26)
- TWU Local 252 Metropolitan Suburban Bus Authority, William Mossbrugger, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 27)
- TWU Local 252 Metropolitan Suburban Bus Authority, Ed Williams, et al. - dismissal, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 28)
- TWU Local 252 Metropolitan Suburban Bus Authority, Probationary Employees, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 29)
- TWU Local 252 Metropolitan Suburban Bus Authority, Edward Robert Williams, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 30)
- TWU Local 252 Metropolitan Suburban Bus Authority, William Elrod, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 31)
- TWU and Metro-North Commuter Railroad Co. Misc., 1974-1983 (Box 20, Folder 32)
- UTU and Metro-North Commuter Railroad, Co. Exhibits, personal Notes, Correspondences, 1981-1984 (Box 20, Folder 33)
- UTU and Metro-North Commuter Railroad Co. Corresp. Re-strike, 1982-1984 (Box 20, Folder 34)
- UTU and Metro-North Commuter Railroad Co. Newspaper Clippings, 1982-1988 (Box 20, Folder 35)
- UTU and Metro-north Commuter Railroad co. Hearings Before U.S. Senate, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 36)
- UTU and Metro-north Commuter Railroad co.Stipulators, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  Aprils 15
- UTU and Metro-north Commuter Railroad co. Statement of Interpretation, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 38)
- UTU and Metro-north Commuter Railroad co. Agreement between parties, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 39)
- UTU and Metro-north Commuter Railroad co. Statements by T.W.K., 1983 (Box 20, Folder 40)
- UTU and Metro-north Commuter Railroad co. Statement of Position, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 41)
- UTU and Metro-north Commuter Railroad co. Workload Concurring Opinion, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  Sept 26
- Transport workers Union of America AFL-CIO local 100 and Amalgamated Transit Union AFL-CIO locals 726 and 1056 and New York city Transit Authority and Manhattan and Bronx Surface Transit Operating Authority, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  Aug 18
- Local 100, TWU Local 726 and 1056, ATU and New York City Transit Authority and MABSTOA, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- ATU Div. 726 and 1056, TWU, local 100 and NYCTA and MABSTOA, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Local 100, TWU and Locals 726 and 1056, ATU and MABSTOA and NYCTA, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Locals 1061 and 1181, ATU, and Local 252, TWU and Metro Sub. Bus authority Agreement, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- ATU Locals 1061, 1181, TWU Local 252; Metropolitan Suburban Bus Authority, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Locals 1181 and Local, ATU, and local 252, TWU and MSBA, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Local 100, TWU and locals 726 and 1056, ATU and NYC Transit Authority Louis Bauso, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Local 100, TWU and Locals 726 and 1056, ATU, NYC Transit Authority, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Locals 1181 and 1061, Amalgamated Transit Union and Local 252, TWU, and Metropolitan Suburban Bus Authority, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- ATU Locals 1061, 1181l TWU local 252; MSBA, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Locals 1181 and 1061, ATU and Local 252, TWU and MSBA, Slow Down, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Locals 1181 and 1061, Amal. Transit Union Local 252 TWU of America and Metropolitan Suburban Bus Authority Pick Schedule, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- ATU local 1181-1061; TWU Local 252; MSBA Agreement, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Locals 1181 and 1061, ATU and Local 252, TWU and MSBA Herbert Jackson, et al., 1976 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Local 1881 and 1061, ATU and Local 252, TWU and MSBA Dispatcher Selection, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Locals 1181 and 1061, ATU and Local 252, TWU, and MSBA John Grandieri, et al., 1976 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Locals 1181 and 1061, Amal. Transit Union Local 252, TWU of America and Metropolitan Suburban Bus Authority, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 18)
- Local 252, TWU of America Local 1181-1061 Amal. Transit Union suburban Bus Auth. Uniforms, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 19)
- Local 1061, ATU and Local 252, TWU and MSBA, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  April 27
- Local 1181 and 1061, ATU and Local 252, TWU and MSBA, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 21)
- Local 252, TWU and Locals 1181 and 1061, ATU and MSBA John and M. Heyanke, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 22)
- Local 1061, ATU and Local 252, TWU and MSBA Pick-runs, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 23)
- Local 252, TWU and Locals 1061 and 1181, ATU and MSBA Repick, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 24)
- Locals 1181 and 1061, ATU Local 252, TWU and MSBA, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 25)
- Locals 1181 and 1061, ATU and Local 252, TWU and Metropolitan Suburban Bus Authority, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 26)
- Local 100, TWU of America Locals 726 and 1056, Amal. Transit Union and NYCTA MABSTOA, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 27)
- Local 100, TWU and Locals 726 and 1056, ATU and MABSTOA and NYCTA, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 28)
- Local 100, TWU, and Locals 726 and 1056, ATU, and MABSTOA and NYCTA, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 29)
- Lutz Lawrence Re: Domenico Bus Transit Industry, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Brochures and Pamphlets of Fifth Avenue Coach Co., 1938-1946 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Metropolitan Suburban Bus Authority, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- New York City Mayor's Advisory Transit committee, 1946 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Organizations Representing Hourly Paid employees of the authority and NYC Transit Authority, 1954 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- All Interested Employee Organizations and New York city Authority, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- All Interested Employee Organizations and New York City Transit authority, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Awards Involving Individuals and NYC Transit Authority (Box 22, Folder 8)
- New York State Board of Meditation - correspondence and Memoranda, 1946-1957 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Misc. - Liberty Coaches, Airport Trans./Riversdale Bertram, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  May
- Eastern, Southeastern, and Western Railroads represented by the National Railway Labor conference and Shop Craft Employees, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Railroads represented by Eastern Western and Southeastern Carriers Conference committees and the Employees of such Railroads Represented by the Brotherhood of railroad Trainmen, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Certain Employees Represented by the Brotherhood Locomotive Engineers, Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen and Certain Carriers by the Eastern Western and Southeastern carriers conference committees, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- National Railway conference and East Western and Southeastern Carriers Conference Committees and the Employees of such Carriers, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Manhattan and Bronx Surface Transit Operating authority and NYCTA, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Local 100, TWUA, CIO and Fifth Avenue Coach Company, 1946 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Allied Printing Trades Council - correspondences and Photographs, 1981-1983 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Actors Equity Association and the Liza Company, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Picardy Mills, Inc. and ACWA CIO, 1953 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  June 2
- Frederick Loeser and Company, and AFL Organization Council, 1948 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Local 802, America Federation of Musicians, and Metropolitan opera Ass., 1962 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  Feb 27
- Allen B. DuMont Labs, and America Federation of television, and Radio Artists, AFC, 1955 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- American Football League Players Association and American Football League, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- American Guild of Variety Artists and Radio City Musical Hall Corp., 1968 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Association of National Baseball League Umpires and The American League of Professional Baseball Clubs, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Edward Frank Ball and Bakery and Confectionery Union and Industry Nat'l Pension Fund Pension Application, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Robert W. Patridse and Bakery and Confectionery Union and Industry Nat'l Pension Fund - Pension Application, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Bakery and Confectionery Union and Industry Nat'l Pension Fund and "Strike Time", 1958 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Bakery and confectionery Union and Industry Nat'l workforce Fund and Welfare Benefits, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  Oct 13
- Rule of Delinquency and Bakery and Confectionery Union and Industry Nat'l Pension Fund, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  Nov 13
- Pedro Gonzalez and Bakery and confectionery Union and Industry Nat'l Pension Fund, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- George H. Marquette and Bakery and confectionery Union and Industry Nat'l Pension fund, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 16)
- Welfare Fund v Pension Fund, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- Bakery and confectionery Union and Industry Int'l Pension fund, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- Thomas Otto Dawson, et al. Under the Bakery and confectionery Union and Industry Int'l Pension Fund, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 19)
- Bakery and confectionery Union and Industry Int'l Pension Fund, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  Feb 21
- Alvin Burks Bakery and confectionery Union and Industry Int'l Welfare fund, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 21)
- Bakery and Confectionery Union and Industry Int'l Pension Fund, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 22)
- Bakery and confectionery Union and Industry Int'l Pension Fund, and Bakery and Confectionery Union Industry International Welfare, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 23)
- William I Massey Under Bakery and confectionery Union and Industry Int'l Pension Fund, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 24)
- Local 125, Bakery and confectionery Union and Industry Int'l Pension Fund, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 25)
- Bakery and confectionery Union and Industry Int'l Pension Fund and McGavin Toastmaster, Ltd., 1968 (Box 23, Folder 26)
- Bakery and confectionery Union and Industry Int'l Pension Fund Ennst Strauss, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  Aug 22
- continental Bakery and confectionery Union and Industry Int'l Welfare Fund, 1955 (Box 23, Folder 28)
- Bakery and confectionery Union and Industry Int'l Pension Fund and Ebinger Baking Company, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 29)
- Nu-way Market Division of American State and Bakery and confectionery Union and Industry Nat'l Pension fund, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 30)
- Scudder food Products, Bell Brand Food Products, Tom Sawyer Foods - Local 400, and Bakery confectionery Union and industry International Welfare Fund, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 31)
- Bricklayers, Masons, and Plasterers Int'l Union and Building Contractors and Mason Builders Association of New York correspondences, 1948-1950 (Box 23, Folder 32)
- Rendering Industry Employees Group Inc., and Local 640, butcher workmen's Union of New York and New Jersey, AFL, 1953 (Box 23, Folder 33)
- Chattanooga Typographical union No. 89 and Times Printing Company, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  aug 2
- CAFTCSOSW, Local 147, of NY, NJ and Vicinity, and SA Healey Company Eugene J Hickey, 1955 (Box 23, Folder 35)
- George H. Flinn corp. and Mason and Hanger co. Int. and CAFTCSCSCW, Local 147, AFL, 1950 (Box 23, Folder 36)
- CAFTCSCSW, Local 147, of NY, NJ, and Vicinity, and Mason and Hanger co., The Arthur A Johnson Corp., Maclean Group company, 1955 (Box 23, Folder 37)
- CAFTCSCSW, Local 147, of NY, NJ, and vicinity, and Mason and Hanger Co., Inc., the Arthur A Johnson corp., MacLean - Grove company, Inc., 1956 (Box 23, Folder 38)
- Transcripts - Matter between Compressed Air Foundation, tunnel, Caisson, Subway, cofferdam, Sewer construction workers, Local No. 147 of NY, NJ states and vicinity of AFL, and Mason and Hanger, 10, Arthur A Johnson corp. MacLean - Grove, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 39)
- Compressed air, Foundation, Tunnel, Caisson, Subway, cofferdam, Sewer Construction Worker's Local 147 of NY, NJ and Vicinity, AFL, and Mason and Hanger Co., Inc., the Arthur A Johnson corp. MacLean Grove co., 1956 (Box 23, Folder 40)
- Local 56 - firemen, Oilers, and Maintenance Mechanics, and Brewers Board of Trade, Inc. on Behalf of Jacob Rupert Brewery, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 41)
- Flight engineers Int'l Ass, and American Airlines, Inc. Augustin C Romano, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 42)
- Campbell soup Comp., and Food, Tobacco, Agricultural and allied Workers, Local 80, CIO, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 43)
- fort Pitt Lodge No. 1 of the Fraternal Order of Police, and City of Pittsburgh, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 44)
- General Industrial Workers Union, Local 146, AFL-CIO and General Airline and Film Corp., 2003 (Box 23, Folder 45)
- Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders Union, Local 418, and New Irving Hotel, Julius Kaplan, et al., 1962 (Box 23, Folder 46)
  Sept 20
- Ice Cream Drivers and Employees Union Local 757 and Whitelawn Diaries, 1946 (Box 23, Folder 47)
  Aug. 22
- Underwood corporation and Lodge No. 19, Int'l Association of Machinists, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 48)
- Underwood Corp. and Lodge No. 350, Int'l Association of Machinists Antoinette Grasso, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 49)
  Dec 3
- Vender - Root Incorporated, and Int'l Association of Machinists, Capitol City, Lodge No. 354, 1953 (Box 23, Folder 50)
- Int'l Ass. Of Machinists, Local 946, and Aerojet - General Corporation, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 51)
- Lodge 1125, Int'l Association of Machinists, and CONVAIR, San Diego, a division of General Dynamics corporation, Thomas Joseph Barrett, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 52)
- American Hardware corporation and Lodge 1137, Int'l Association of Machinists, 1955 (Box 23, Folder 53)
- Lodges 19, 350, and 354, International ass. Of Machinists, AFL-CIO, and Olivetti Underwood Corp. Charles Heck, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 54)
- IBEW AFL-CIO and the Kerite Company, a Subsidiary of Harvey Hubbell, Inc., 1979 (Box 23, Folder 55)
- Hall Baking (Mills Bakery) of continental Baking co., and Bakery Salesman - Drivers Union, Local 51, IBT, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 56)
- Hall Baking (Mills Bakery) of continental Baking Co., and Bakery Salesman - Drivers' Union Local 51, IBT (Box 23, Folder 57)
- Hall Bakery (Mills Bakery) of Continental Baking co. and Bakery Salesmen - Drivers Union, Local 51, IBT (Box 23, Folder 58)
- Hall Baking (Mills Bakery) of continental Baking Co., and Bakery Salesmen - Drivers' Union, Local 51, IBT (Box 23, Folder 59)
- Local 145, IBT, and Manning, Maxwell, and Moore, Inc. Stratford Works, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 60)
- Teamsters Local Union 145 and Frank A Durso Company, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 61)
- Local 282 Truck Drivers, Chauffers and Helpers and N. Ryan Co., Inc. Harry Roggakauf, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 62)
- Brighton Materials co. Inc., et al. and teamsters Local 252, 1955 (Box 23, Folder 63)
- Petelinz Davy and Teamsters Local 338, 1952 (Box 23, Folder 64)
- Local 553, IBT, and Nassau Mutual Fuel comp., Inc., 1977 (Box 23, Folder 65)
- Milk drivers Local 554, IBT, and Beers Inc., 1967 (Box 23, Folder 66)
- Milk Drivers Local 584, IBT, and Dellwood Davy Co., Inc., 1967 (Box 23, Folder 67)
- Milk Drivers Local 584, IBT, and Grandview Dairy, Inc., 1960 (Box 23, Folder 68)
- Milk Drivers Local 584, IBT and Queens Farms Dairy Co. Michael Friseuda, et al., 1967 (Box 23, Folder 69)
- Milk Driver's Local 584, IBT, and Richmore Processing corp., 1968 (Box 23, Folder 70)
- Milk Drivers Local 584, IBT and Sunnydale Farms, Inc., et al., 1966 (Box 23, Folder 71)
- Milk Drivers Local 584, IBT, and Weissglass Gold seal Dairy corp., 1967 (Box 23, Folder 72)
- Local 707 (affiliated w/ Teamsters) and Carolina Freight Carriers Corp. Inc. John Mahady, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 73)
- IBT Local 757 Agreement, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 74)
- Teamsters Local 804 and United Parcel Service, Inc., 1963 (Box 23, Folder 75)
- Teamsters Local 805 and Global Frozen foods, Inc. and Employees and group A and Group B, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 76)
  June 12
- Teamsters Local 805 and NY Automatic Canteen Corporation, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 77)
- National Biscuit Co. and Truck Drivers Local Union 807 Michael Hrize, et al., 1956 (Box 23, Folder 78)
- Teamsters Local 807 and Sidney S. Schupper Interstate Hauling System, Inc., 1949 (Box 23, Folder 79)
- Jus. Schlitz Brewing co. and Brewery Workers Local 1345, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 80)
- Jos. Schlitz Brewing co. and Brewery Workers Local Union 1345, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 81)
- Jos. Schlitz Brewing Co. and Brewery Workers Local 1345, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 82)
  Jan 12
- Jos. Schlitz Brewing co. and Brewery Workers Local 1345, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 83)
- Jos. Schlitz Brewing co. and Brewery Workers Local 1345, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 84)
- TBT, Brewery workers Union, Local 1345, and Liebmann Brewers, Inc., 1951 (Box 23, Folder 85)
- Jacob Ruppert, Liebmann Breweries, Inc., Piel Bros., Piel's Inc., and TGF adm. Schaefer Brewing Co. and Int'l Brhd of Teamsters, etc. and Brewery Local 1, 8, 124, 1059, 323, 1956 (Box 23, Folder 86)
- Brewery Worker's Local Unions 124 and 1345, Teamsters, and Liebmann Breweries, Inc. F Cernera, et al., 1960 (Box 23, Folder 87)
- Brewery Workers Local Unions 124 and 1345, Teamsters, Liebmann Breweries, Inc., 1961 (Box 23, Folder 88)
- Brewery Workers Local 124, 1345, Teamsters and Liebmann Breweries, Inc. Mr. F Cernera, et al., 1961 (Box 23, Folder 89)
- Brewery workers Local Unions 124, 1345, Teamsters and Liebmann Breweries, Inc., 1963 (Box 23, Folder 90)
- Various corps. And Locals 145, 199, 550, 802 - teamsters, 1952 (Box 23, Folder 91)
- Milk Drivers Locals 584, 602, and 607 Re: company Stores and other Outlets (Box 23, Folder 92)
- Local 142, Int'l Federation of technical Engineers, AFL-CIO and GE Comp, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 93)
- Warehousemen' Ass. Of the Port of New York, Inc. and Int'l Longshoremen's Ass, 1949 (Box 23, Folder 94)
- Int'l Longshoremen's Association, and NY shipping Association, Inc., 1966 (Box 23, Folder 95)
- Int'l Longshoremen's Association, and NY Shipping Association, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 96)
- Int'l Longshoremen's Ass. And NY Shipping Association, Inc., 1968 (Box 23, Folder 97)
- Orion shipping and Trading co., Inc., and Agents for Colonial Steamship Corp. and Int'l Organization of Masters, and Pilots Charles Medlin, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 98)
- Int'l Union of electrical, Radio and Machine Workers and GE Comp Frank Luongo, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 99)
- Int'l Union of electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, and GE Company Supplementary Award, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 100)
- Ingersoll-Rand Company and Local 313, Int'l Union of electrical Radio and Machine workers, David Davis, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 101)
- International Union of electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers AFL-CIO Local 317 and Foster Refrigerator Corporation, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 102)
- Local 323, IUE and General Railway Signal company E Vollmer, 1954 (Box 23, Folder 103)
- local 323 IUE and General Railway Signal Company, 1954 (Box 23, Folder 104)
- Local 323 Int'l Union of Electrical Radio and Machine Workers, and general Railway Signal comp. Dewitt Proctor, 1955 (Box 23, Folder 105)
  Oct 11
- Local 323, Int'l Union of electrical Radio, and Machine workers and general Railway Signal company Harry Devlin, 1955 (Box 23, Folder 106)
- General railway Signal Corp. and Local 323, Int'l Union of electrical Radio, and Machine Workers, 1956 (Box 23, Folder 107)
- Local 323, Int'l Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers, and General Railway Signal Comp. Ralph Huff, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 108)
- Local 323, IUE, and General Railway Signal Company, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 109)
- Local 323, IUE, and General Railway Signal Company, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 110)
- Local 323, IUE, and General Railway Signal Company, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 111)
- Local 323, Int'l Union of electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers, and General Railway Signal Comp. John Chadsey, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 112)
- Local 323, Int'l Union of electrical, Radio, and Machine workers, and General Railway Signal comp. Lloyd Tipton`, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 113)
- local 323, Int'l Union of electrical, Radio, and Machine workers and General Railway signal company, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 114)
- local 323, Int'l Union of electrical, Radio, and Machine workers and General Railway signal company, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 115)
- local 323, Int'l Union of electrical, Radio, and Machine workers and General Railway signal company, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 116)
- Local 400, Professional, Technical and Salaried Division, Int'l Union of electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, AFL-CIO, and Int'l Telephone and Telegraph corporation, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 117)
  Aug 3
- Local 400 Professional, Technical and Salaried Division, Int'l Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers, AFL-CIO, and Int'l Telephone and Telegraph Corp. (A Maryland Corp.), 1961 (Box 23, Folder 118)
- local 434, Int'l Union of electrical, Radio, and Machine workers and PR Mallory and Co. James Clark, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 119)
- Local 447, International Union of electrical, Radio and Machine workers, AFL-CIO, and Fed. Telephone and Radio company, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 120)
  Aug 5